// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let Maths = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which among the following chemicals is used in Photography?",
    answer: "[A] Silver Bromide",
    options: [
      "[A] Silver Bromide",
      "[B] Potassium Chloride",
      "[C] Sodium Bromide",
      "[D] Magnesium Chloride"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Kazimierz Funk or Casimir Funk, was a Polish biochemist, generally credited with the first formulation of the concept of which of the following ?",
    answer:  "[D] Vitamins",
    options: [
      "[A] Amino Acids",
      "[B] DNA",
      "[C] RNA",
      "[D] Vitamins"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following chemicals is used as a molecular sieve to filter common salts from seawater to produce potable water?",
    answer:  "[A] Graphene oxide",
    options: [
      "[A] Graphene oxide",
      "[B] Phosgene",
      "[C] Sodium hypochlorite",
      "[D] Calcium carbonate"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the stress known as when there is a relative displacement between various layers of solid?",
    answer:"[A] Tangential",
    options: [
      "[A] Tangential",
      "[B] Linear",
      "[C] Lateral",
      "[D] Longitudinal"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the maximum stress after which the wire breaks called as?",
    answer:   "[A] Tensile strength", 
    options: [
      "[A] Tensile strength",
      "[B] Shear strength",
      "[C] Bulk strength",
      "[D] Hooke’s strength"
    ]
  },
  {
      numb: 6,
      question:"What is the maximum stress after which the wire breaks called as?",
      answer: "[A] Tensile strength",
      options:[
        "[A] Tensile strength",
        "[B] Shear strength",
        "[C] Bulk strength",
        "[D] Hooke’s strength"
      ]
  },
 {
     numb: 7,
     question: "What is the maximum stress after which the wire breaks called as?",
     answer: "[A] Tensile strength",
      options:[
        "[A] Tensile strength",
        "[B] Shear strength",
        "[C] Bulk strength",
        "[D] Hooke’s strength"
      ]
 },
 {
     numb: 8,
     question: "Which of the following alkali metal ions has the highest hydration enthalpy?",
     answer:  "[A] Lithium",
     options:[
         "[A] Lithium",
         "[B] Sodium",
         "[C] Potassium",
         "[D] Caesium"

     ]
 },
 {
    numb: 9,
     question: "What is the general electron configuration of all alkaline earth metals?",
     answer:  "[B] ns2",
     options:[
         "[A] ns1",
         "[B] ns2",
         "[C] ns2 np6",
         "[D] None of the above"

     ]
 },
 {
    numb: 10,
     question: "What is the property of matter by which a body tends to regain its original configuration after the removal of deforming force known as?",
     answer:  "[C] Elasticity",
     options:[
         "[A] Plasticity",
         "[B] Ductility",
         "[C] Elasticity",
         "[D] Malleability"

     ]
 }
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];